JAAN SANGHA

www.jaansangha.com | jaansangha10@gmail.com | 289-500-5226

GAME PROGRAMMER / FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Knowledgeable and detail-oriented entry level programmer with experience working in a fast-paced environment. Solid familiarity gained in developing video games through various projects and a 3-year program taken with George Brown. Highly developed technical and analytical skills with experience in working as part of an efficient and goal-oriented team. Strong communication skills with ability to resolve problems with a calm and professional demeanor.

Technical Proficiency:

• Languages: C++, C#, Java, C, Swift, Python, JavaScript

• Other: Unity, Unreal Engine 4, HTML 5, CSS, Git, Trello, Perforce

EDUCATION

Ontario College Advanced Diploma: Game Programming

George Brown College

Graduated April 2022

Toronto, ON

Major Units of Study: Advanced programming, Artificial Intelligence, Mathematics, Data Structures and Algorithms, Game Physics, 3D Graphics Programming, Game Engines, Game production, Console Game Development, Multiplayer Systems, Mobile Game Development etc.

The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp

Completed August 2023

Udemy

Major Units of Study: Flexbox, Bootstrap, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, Git, API's, SQL and NoSQL databases, MongoDB, Mongoose, Authentication and Security, React.js.

RELATED PROJECTS

Cardemon

September 2022 - Current

- Currently working on a turn based combat game that has many popular RPG elements like; card collecting, melee combat, farming, crafting.
- Built With: Unity, C#

Roly Controly

February 2023 - Current

- Currently working on a mobile game where the player uses their device accelerometer to move the ball around and complete different levels.
- The game is currently in early access on the Play Store.
- Built With: Unity, C#

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Game Developer

March 2023 - Current

Nibbit.ai

Toronto, ON

- Brainstorm and design mini game concepts and elements by coordinating with the design team
- Develop frameworks and translate design ideas into clean and efficient code by deploying game engine
- Test game features and ensure bug free releases

IOS SUPPORT ADVISOR

May 2022 - September 2022

Apple (Contract)

Toronto, ON

- Identify and solve complex technical problems with work-issued programs based on customer feedback and needs
- Develop a strong knowledge of Apple products in order to provide accurate and efficient support to all customers
- Used CRM technology to log and provide accurate solutions to all customers